right papilloma ten last Apple for the
day maybe might be on later again one
more ideas coming I wanted to like force
is the wrong word but allow the first
ten apples to happen on the first day to
show that more will come because these
are some of my ideas that have come up
over the last few years so happy them
all out the first day is is pretty he's
amazing is it clears me out for new ones
and so number ten you can talk about
done apples an Apple Apple okay
another level I would like a gardening
yeah I'm sure they exist I'm positive
they exist but a fruit one that is
amazing that everyone can it will tell
me what to grow where what to grow in my
neighborhood with my climb and I'll be
like by the way everyone else in your
neighborhoods peas already your European
so that we can use the data of everyone
to to work together that I can work with
my neighbors and say hey I grow too many
tomatoes lots tomatoes I forgot to grow
cucumbers or my Cuban farmers died who
has cucumbers to be able to yeah so
that's probably more than one out there
but to be able to grow in my yard be
able to take pictures leave little data
points out little sensors and have it
tell me here's a much Sun happens on a
sunny day or so much rain like it hasn't
rained you might want to go water your
plant and it beeps Andy it's not a
memory for that and even though it's
like oh it's hot and dry I'm drinking
water fifty times today
maybe I should water my plants to be
able to crowdsource solutions to fungus
problems and pests and people the more
you just easily follow permaculture
principles which allows you to garden
without a lot of the work and then I can
say okay well I have tons of tomatoes
and tons of strawberries at this moment
what can I make with them probably not
together but what can I make what can I
utilize and so the more we're able to
use technology to come together as a
community and
we're able to use technology to use the
knowledge of the crowd
I just believe there's so many ways
there are nearly infinite number of ways
to help us eat better I II have it won't
be more delicious have it be more
community centered and have it be more
accessible to everyone and so idea
number 10 is a gardening app so being
able to tell where to plant but and how
to best grow it as well as what yields
iPads so that I can we can figure out
maybe someone's yard is amazing for
growing tomatoes they can grab Tomatoes
for the entire entire block
and maybe you have a yard you don't you
would be willing to have someone else
gardening but you don't want a garden in
it and so yeah that is in combination of
gardening app with the community app to
be able to combine with your neighbors
90 number 10